Guide to the James Snead Papers, 1966-1989 UA.90.F81
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Personal Activities, 1967-1990; III.
  - English 57 Introduction to American Literature Course Book (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Faulkner Conference Notice, August 2-7th, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - "Homer and the Literary Tradition" Lecture Disc Notes (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Honoring of Elizabeth I at Yale, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Introduction to Panel on "The Limits of Symbolism" (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Information for Advising, August 1982 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - "Mass Culture in America Today" Lecture (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Music and Drawing (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Nietzsche Lecture (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Photos of Snead and Band (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Snead Notes and Papers for English 32, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "The Underground and the Essential in Ellison's Invisible Man" Lecture, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1980-1994; IV.
  This series contains regular correspondence, as well as parody correspondence. The correspondence is to, from, and about James Snead. The letters range from 1980 to 1994.
  - Correspondence, 1980-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Parody Letters (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Research on James Snead, V.
  This series contains notecards created by Colin MacCabe and Kara Keeling who cataloged a portion of the papers found in this collection before they were deposited in the University of Pittsburgh Archives. The notes outline some of the unidentified works by Snead and aided in the oranization of this collection.
  - Notecards (Box 5, Folder 5)